clubtexting.com 2016-04-13

# About Club Texting | Club Texting

Thank you for visiting our site at www.clubtexting.com (" _Website_ ").  This privacy policy covers the websites www.clubtexting.com. Use and access of this Website is subject to the terms and conditions as set out in our Terms of Service as well as our Privacy Policy set forth below.

[](https://privacy.truste.com/privacy-seal/Ez-Texting/validation?rid=14f9d4fe-e368-4f85-866e-6300ecc70d62 "TRUSTe online privacy certification") Club Texting has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information.  TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [info@clubtexting.com](mailto:info@clubtexting.com), by phone, chat, email, or postal mail.  If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, and does not cover information that may be collected through our applications.

**1\. General**  
Your privacy is important to us and we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the collection and use of the personal information you submit at this Website.    

If you are visiting the Website from outside the United States, please be advised that your personal data will be processed by Club Texting in the United States where data protection and privacy regulations may differ from similar regulations in other countries.  By using the Website, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country if you are located outside of the United States.  Additionally, by using the Website, you consent to Club Texting using your personal information to contact you electronically, in writing, or otherwise to provide notices relating to your use of the Website and to give you information about the products and services offered by Club Texting and its affiliates.  If you would like to opt out of future promotional materials from us, you may indicate this preference by following the unsubscribe instructions at the end of such communications from us. 

**2\. Personally-Identifiable Information**  
In order to purchase products or services from Club Texting, we require that you provide us with certain personally identifiable information (please see our _Terms of Service_ for additional details). The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected by Club Texting through the Website include, without limitation: name, address, e-mail address, cell phone number and MSISDN (mobile station integrated services digital network number), credit card and billing information, download history, texts, messages, customer generated content and/or information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.  Club Texting will not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily. 

Please know that you will retain ownership of any information that you may include in your account and contact lists in order to identify recipients of your messages through Club Texting’s services, and Club Texting will not use contact lists for its own promotional campaigns or sell contact lists to third-parties, subject at all times to Club Texting’s need to access and use such information in order to provide the services pursuant to its Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy.

We may use such personally identifiable information to provide the services that you have requested, to contact you about programs, products, features or services in which we believe you may be interested (such as future promotional materials), or for other purposes disclosed from time to time.  We also may use your personally identifiable information to contact you regarding your use of our Website or changes to our Privacy Policy, _Terms of Service_ , or other policies or terms that affect you and your use of our Website and services.  In addition, we may use information collected about our users to improve the content and navigation of our Website, or for other internal purposes.

To fulfill your requests for products and services, we may share the personally identifiable information you provide with your cell phone service provider or their partner and subcontractor companies. Please know that this Privacy Policy does not cover such entities use of information. To learn more about your provider’s privacy practices, you should consult its privacy policy.

We also use third party service providers such as an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf. We use Live Chat to assist you if you have questions while using our site or regarding our service. When you sign up for our services, we will share your personal information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

In addition, we may disclose personally identifiable information collected about you in the following instances:  

  * **A. Legal Action:** We may disclose information about our users, including personally identifiable information; (i) when requested by governmental or quasi-governmental authorities conducting an investigation; (ii) if required to do so by subpoena, court order or legal process; (iii) to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws; or (iv) to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website. We also may disclose user information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability; to protect or defend our rights or property; or protect the safety, rights, or property of our users.
  * **B. Change in Control:** We may sell, transfer, or otherwise disclose user information, including personally identifiable information, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, the sale of substantially all assets, or other corporate change respecting Club Texting, the Website and/or the services offered hereby.

Except as stated in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise stated at the time personally-identifiable information is gathered, Club Texting will not provide personally-identifiable information to third parties who are not under the direction and control of Club Texting. 

**3\. Access to Personal Information**  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [info@clubtexting.com](mailto:info@clubtexting.com). We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

**4\. Cookies**  
We use cookies to make interactions with the Company's Website easy and meaningful. When you visit one of the Company's Websites, our servers send a cookie to your computer. Standing alone, cookies do not personally identify you. They merely recognize your Web browser. Unless you choose to identify yourself to us, either by responding to a promotional offer, opening an account, or filling out a Web form (such as a "Contact Me" or a "30 Day Free Trial" Web form), you remain anonymous to the Company.

There are two types of cookies: session-based and persistent-based. Session cookies exist only during one session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser software or turn off your computer. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you close your browser or turn off your computer.

If you have chosen to identify yourself to us, the Company uses session cookies containing encrypted information to allow the Company to uniquely identify you. Each time you log into the Service, a session cookie containing an encrypted, unique identifier that is tied to your account is placed on your browser. These session cookies allow the Company to uniquely identify you when you are logged into the Service and to process your online transactions and requests. Session cookies are required to use the Service and the Company does not recognize do-not-track requests with respect to Session cookies.

We use persistent cookies that only the Company can read and use to identify browsers that have previously visited the Company's Websites. When you purchase the Service or provide the Company with personal information, a unique identifier is assigned you. This unique identifier is associated with a persistent cookie that the Company places on your Web browser. The Company is especially careful about the security and confidentiality of the information stored in persistent cookies. For example, the Company does not store account numbers or passwords in persistent cookies. If you disable your Web browser's ability to accept cookies, you will be able to navigate the Company's Web sites, but you will not be able to successfully use the Service. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a persistent cookie, or you may choose to block persistent cookies with your browser. Additionally, we will not place persistent cookies on any computer where the browser provides a “do-not-track” signal. However, if your settings block cookies and tracking, you may not be able to take advantage of the personalized features enjoyed by other users to our Site. 

We may use information from session and persistent cookies in combination with Data about our Customers to provide you with information about the Company and the Service. 

**Third Party Cookies**

From time-to-time, we engage third parties to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from individuals who visit the Company's Web sites. We may also use other third-party cookies to track the performance of Company advertisements. The information provided to third parties does not include personal information, but this information may be re-associated with personal information after the Company receives it. This Privacy Statement does not cover the use of third party cookies. We will not place third-party cookies on any computer where the browser provides a “do-not-track” signal. 

**5\. Web Beacons**  
Our third party advertising partners employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users.  In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. 

**6\. Children**  
The Website is not directed at individuals less than thirteen (13) years of age, and Club Texting does not intend to collect any personally-identifiable information from such individuals, unless otherwise stated at the time such information is collected.   

**7\. Information Collected Automatically**  
Club Texting may also (i) automatically collect non-personally-identifiable information about your use of the Website, such as the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, Comcast.net, if you are connecting from a Comcast account), the date and time you access the Website, and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our Website; and (ii) use data capture and analysis tools, and other similar tools, to extract, compile and analyze any non-personally identifiable data or information resulting from your use of the Website and the services offered thereon (collectively “ _Blind Data_ ”).  To the extent that any Blind Data is collected by Club Texting, such Blind Data shall be solely owned by Club Texting and may be used by Club Texting for any lawful business purpose, including, without limitation, analyzing and enhancing the Website and services offered hereby, disclosing such Blind Data to third parties for a variety of purposes.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites on the internet.
  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a   
user's prior visits to our website.
  * Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies   
by [visiting the Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**  
8\. Testimonials**  
We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to request to have your testimonial removed you may contact us at [info@clubtexting.com](mailto:info@clubtexting.com).

**9\. Public Forums**  
Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [info@clubtexting.com](mailto:info@clubtexting.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**10\. Links to Other Websites**  
The Website may contain links to third party websites, whose information practices may be different than Club Texting’s. Visitors should consult such third-party sites’ privacy notices as Club Texting does not have any control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.  Club Texting does not make any representations or warranties as to the security of any information (including, without limitation, credit card and other personal information) you might be requested to give any third party.    

These links are provided solely as a convenience to you and not as an endorsement by Club Texting of the contents on such third-party websites.  Club Texting cannot ensure that you will be satisfied with any products or services that you purchase from a third-party site that links to or from the Website, since these sites are owned and operated by independent retailers.  

Club Texting is not responsible for the content of linked third-party sites and does not make any representations regarding the content or accuracy of materials on such third-party sites.  Club Texting has not taken any steps to confirm the accuracy or reliability of any of the information contained in such third-party sites.  If you decide to access linked third-party sites, you do so at you own risk. Club Texting strongly encourages you to make whatever investigation you feel necessary or appropriate before proceeding with any online or off-line transaction with any of these third parties. 

**11\. Data Security**  
The importance of security for all personally-identifiable information associated with visitors to the Website—as well as Club Texting customer information, such as cell phone numbers, texts, messages and other account data—is of utmost concern to Club Texting, and we have implemented, and periodically review, certain physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to help prevent unauthorized access and maintain data security. Unfortunately, due to the open nature of Internet communications, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be secure, and thus we cannot guarantee that communications between you and Club Texting will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. Visitors of the Website and Club Texting customers use the Website at their own risk.

**12\. Your Acceptance of These Terms**  
By accessing the Website, you signify your assent to the Club Texting Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not access the Website. You should visit this page periodically, as we may, from time to time, update this Privacy Policy and such changes shall be effectively immediately upon posting on the Website and without further notice to you.  Your continued access to the Website following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy shall be deemed an acceptance of such changes by you.  Club Texting will, however, use personally-identifiable information only in accordance with the version of the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected. 

**13\. Changes in This Privacy Policy**  
We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Questions/Concerns?**   
If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us. You may also contact us via postal mail at PO Box 1973, Santa Monica, CA 90406.

Last updated December 2012.
